const data = [
    {
        id: '1' ,
        question: 'How can I contact the restaurant?' ,
        answer: 'You can reach us by phone at 030478905 , or by email at support@foodfusion.com. You can also visit our contact page for additional details.' 
    } ,
    {
        id: '2' ,
        question: 'Are you open on holidays?' ,
        answer: 'We are open on most holidays, but please check our website or give us a call to confirm our hours during holiday periods.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '3' ,
        question: 'What are your restaurant hours?' ,
        answer: 'We are open Monday to Sunday from 11:00 AM to 10:00 PM.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '4' ,
        question: 'Do you offer takeout or delivery?' ,
        answer: 'Yes! We offer both takeout and delivery through our website .' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '5' ,
        question: 'Do you accept reservations?' ,
        answer: 'Yes, we accept reservations. You can book a table via our website or by calling us directly at 030478905.' 
    } ,
    {
        id: '6' ,
        question: 'Do you offer gluten-free options?' ,
        answer: 'Yes, we offer a variety of gluten-free options. Please ask your server for recommendations or check our menu for marked gluten-free dishes.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '7' ,
        question: ' Is your food suitable for vegetarians/vegans?' ,
        answer: 'Yes, we have a selection of vegetarian and vegan-friendly dishes. Look for the vegan symbol on our menu.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '8' ,
        question: 'Do you accommodate food allergies?' ,
        answer: 'Yes, we take food allergies seriously. Please inform your server of any allergies, and we’ll ensure your meal is prepared safely.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '9' ,
        question: `Do you offer a kids' menu?` ,
        answer: ' Yes, we offer a kid-friendly menu with a variety of delicious options suitable for children.' 
    }    ,
    {
        id: '10' ,
        question: 'Do you have a loyalty program?' ,
        answer: 'Yes, we offer a loyalty program. Sign up on our website to receive points for each purchase, and enjoy exclusive discounts and promotions.' 
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '11' ,
        question: 'Do you provide free Wi-Fi?' ,
        answer: `Yes, we offer free Wi-Fi to all our customers. Ask your server for the Wi-Fi details.`
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '12' ,
        question: 'Can I customize my order?' ,
        answer: `Yes, we allow customization! Let your server know any specific preferences, and we'll do our best to accommodate your request.`
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '13' ,
        question: 'What types of payment do you accept?' ,
        answer: `We accept all major credit and debit cards, cash, and mobile payment methods like Sada Pay , Apple Pay and Google Pay.`
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '14' ,
        question: ' What is your specialty dish?' ,
        answer: `Our signature dish is the Velvet Mushroom Pasta . It’s made with fresh, locally sourced ingredients and is a favorite among our regular customers.`
    }
    ,
    {
        id: '15' ,
        question: 'Do you offer group dining or private dining options?' ,
        answer: ` Yes, we offer both group dining and private dining options. Please contact us to discuss your event details and make arrangements.`
    }
]
 export default data;

